NETWORK ENGINEER

Summary

Network Engineer. Qualifications include Secret security clearance, 3.5 years experience in Network Engineering & Implementation, 1 year experience in Server Virtualization & Administration, knowledge of DoD security procedures, leadership capability managing a team to accomplish tasks and projects.

Certifications & Skills

- Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA) (06/16)
- CompTIA Network + (06/18)
- CompTIA Security + (06/18)
- Secret security clearance
- Critical/ Analytical thinking
- Leadership
- Event & Operations experience

Accomplishments

Coordinated with MDA Network Engineers to troubleshoot and fix SFP GBIC compatibility issues between the new switch & Wyse Zero Clients

Experience

Honest Networks Philadelphia, PA Network Engineer 03/2011 to 06/2014

- Coordinated with senior advisers to design networks to meet the needs of military operations.
- Built and maintained networks in a tactical environment, including satellite WAN connections.
- Hardened all systems in compliance with DoD STIG policies
- Monitored and maintained all IT equipment

21St Century Oncology Jupiter, FL IT Procurement Manager 01/2013 to 06/2014

Consulted and advised senior advisers on the procurement of equipment to meet the needs of current and future military operations

Adp Greenville, SC Client Support Administrator 01/2015 to Current

- Troubleshoot hardware & software issues on client systems
- Coordinate with Network Operations Center to troubleshoot network issues
- Configure & maintain MDA mobile devices
- Support MDA VIPs during events

Education

Bachelor of Science: Network Management 2017 Colorado Technical University, City, State, United States High School Diploma 2009 Rye High School, City, State, United States